

#### CONTACT



+866 901 218 716



© @krisridge17\_1



krisridge17@yahoo.com

#### QUALIFICATIONS

# Masters of Arts, Management (MA)

University of Phoenix May 2004

# Bachelor of Applied Science, **Elementary Education (BA)**

University of Minnesota, Duluth

#### **OVFRVIEW**

Professional Network Leadership Community Involvement Curving Environments  Student Welfare Reggio inspired Practitioner	Pedagogical Leadership	Student, Staff & Parent Relationships	Leading Professional Learning
Inclusion Welfare inspired	Network	•	Learning
	Inclusion	~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~ ~	inspired

## CONNECT



LINKEDIN

# KRISTIN L **PARTRIDGE**

#### PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

A trusted and deeply experienced international school teacher leader. Proven ability to collaborate effectively with students, teachers and parent communities to promote the mission and vision of the school. Committed to inquiry-based, constructivist education.

Demonstrated record of success in a variety of key roles spanning IB Programs and American curriculum schools. Student-centered, with a high valued placed on creating caring, culturally inclusive classrooms.

Believes that school communities that value internationalmindedness and build personal connections can create conditions that will inspire the next generation of global citizens as responsible stewards of our world.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Kaohsiung American School**

Grade 1 Teacher 2022-Present Head of Department 2023-Present

#### **United Nations International School Hanoi, Vietnam**

Early Years Homeroom Teacher (3-7 yr olds) 2016-2022 Grade 1 Grade Level Leader 2018-2020 Early Years Grade Level Leader 2016-2017

#### **International School of Tianjin, China**

Early Years Homeroom Teacher 2014-2016

#### Jakarta World Academy/Sinarmas World Academy

Pre-K Homeroom Teacher 2011-2014 **Early Years Coordinator** 2011-2014

#### **Educational Consultant**

Early Childhood Consultant 2000-Present

#### **Stroum Jewish Community Centre**

Early Childhood School Director	2003-2009
Early Childhood Assistant Director	2000-2003
Teacher	1996-2000

# **LEARNING & TEACHING**

#### **EXPERIENCE**

- Established, fostered and promoted positive professional relationships with faculty, parents and students
- Created year-long curriculum overviews and planners with supporting documentation
- Organized local and international early childhood and school age conferences
- Facilitated trainings for teachers and administrators
- Assisted schools to facilitate Reggio Emilia practices in classrooms
- Created Play Based Learning Program 2017-2022
- Created Reading Buddies Program, 2014-16
- Promoted high quality learning environments
- Liaised between boards, administrations, teachers and parents to promote high quality education
- Whole School Assessment Committee Facilitator (IB, WASC, CIS Review)

#### **LEADERSHIP**

- Head of Department & Grade Level Leader
- DEIJ Committee Member
- Faculty Advisory Committee Member
- Social Committee Member
- Summer Camp Teacher
- Lead Teacher Greeter for New Faculty
- EARCOS Teacher Representative
- Workshop Presenter: Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam
- 2 Day Workshop Presenter Kaohsiung, Taiwan
- EARCOS Presenter, Manilla, Philippines
- EARCOS Presenter, Kota Kinabalu, Malaysia
- Organizer, Early Years Summer Camp, UNIS Hanoi
- Workshop Leader: IB Dunia Conference, Jakarta, Indonesia
- Facilitator: IB Job Alike Jakarta, Indonesia
- Workshop Leader and Organizer: Crib to Classroom Head of Department & Grade Level Leader
- Founder & Facilitator: Day of Dialogue Reggio Emilia Network Conferences

# KEY PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT

learning to inspire best practice.

As a reflective practitioner, I seek out professional

- Writer's Workshop Seminars 2022-Present
- Erma Anderson Math Workshops 2022-Present
- Nurturing Reader & Writers with Matt Glover & Kathy Collins, 2020-22
- Story Workshop Studio with Susan Harris MacKay 2021-2022
- Enhancing EY Readers & Writers Through Play, Erin Kent, 2021
- Reggio Emilia Study Tour, 2021 & 2006
- A Peek into the Classroom: Intentionality in the Planning Process with Anne van Dam 2020-2022
- Word Inquiry with Fiona Hamilton 2018-2021
- Social Thinking 2019-2021
- Cognitive Coaching, days 1-4 2018
- Harvard Project Zero: Making Learning Visible, 2018
- Personal, Social and Physical Education-Well Being IB PYP, 2018
- Mentor Teacher for Student Teacher Practicum Candidate 2017-2018 School
   Year
- Learning to Listen in the Early Years with Fiona Zinn, 2017
- Play Based Learning, IB PYP, 2012 & 2017

- Creating Psychological Safety at Work, Fran Perlman 2017
- Responsive Classroom training 2016
- Teacher as Researcher, IB PYP, 2015
- Assessment in the Early Years, IB PYP, 2014
- Symbolic Learning: Literacy and Numeracy in the Early Years IB PYP, 2014
- Circle Solutions for Student Wellbeing by Sue Roffey, 2014
- Concept Based Curriculum with Dr Lynn Erickson, 2013
- Inquiry and Play in the EY Classroom with Jan Millikan 2012
- Learning 2.0 Conference, Beijing, 2012
- Apple Regional Training Workshop: eBook, ePublishing & Digital Storytelling, 2012
- Opal School Workshop, Portland, Oregon, 2012 & 2009
- Inquiry in the Classroom with Kath Murdoch 2011
- Making the PYP Happen, IB PYP, 2011 Teacher Inquiry Group (PYP) 2011-2014
- Learning Stories with Wendy Lee, Karen Ramsey & Tom Drummond, 2008-2009
- In the Spirit of the Studio Conference, St. Louis Reggio Collaborative,

# Contributing to the success and connectedness of school communities is a core value that I hold.

- Innovative School Reggio Emilia Workshop Leader, (English and Bahasa Indonesian), Jakarta, 2014
- IB Dunia (World) Workshop Leader, Jakarta, 2012-2014
- Working in the Reggio Way Workshop Leader, Jakarta, 2011-2013
- North American Reggio Emilia Alliance Member, 2002-2012
- National Association of the Education of Young Children Member, 1997-2012
- Fremont Music School Board Treasurer, Seattle, WA, 2006-2011
- Reggio Emilia Network Founder & Organizer, Seattle, WA, 2005-2011
- United Way Board Member/Family & Children Early Support, Seattle,WA, 2003-2010
  - Day of Dialogue Organizer & Workshop Leader 2008-2010
- Jewish Early Childhood Director Association Board Member, Seattle, WA, 1999-2009
- University of Washington Mentor for Mary Gates Endowment Student Candidate, Seattle, WA, 2008

### COMMUNITY

- Lead New Teacher Greeter and Organizer: UNIS Hanoi 2017-Present and IST 2016
- EARCOS Representative for UNIS, 2018-present
- EY Conference Presenter: Creating an Engaging, Empowering & Playful Environment, Saigon, 2019
- Learning Together Learning Math in an Engaging Way Workshop Presenter (English and Vietnamese), Hanoi, 2019
- Social Committee Chair, UNIS Hanoi 2018-2020
- Grade 5 Exhibition Mentor 2014-2020
- Early Years Conference Presenter: Language Acquisition Through Movement, Saigon, 2018 🌘
- Presenter: Art Exploration from the Early Years to Grade 10 Workshop, EARCOS 2016
- Sunshine Committee Chair and Treasurer, 2014-16, Tianjin International School
- B Middle Years Program Community Action Leader, Tianjin International School, 2014-2016
- Play in the Early Years Two Day Workshop Leader, I-Shou International Kaohsiung, Taiwan, 92016
- Presenter: Play Based Learning in the Early Years Workshop, EARCOS 2015